<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.totalreqall</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>BSD-2-Clause</project_license>
  <name>TotalReqall</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">TotalReqall</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">TotalReqall</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">TotalReqall</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">TotalReqall</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">TotalReqall</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">TotalReqall</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">TotalReqall</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxTotalReqallxx</name>
  <summary>Memorize the Bible or anything else</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Memoritza la Bíblia o qualsevol altre text</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Memoritza la Bíblia o qualsevol altre text</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Memorice la Biblia o cualquier otra cosa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">De Bijbel of iets anders te memoriseren</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Memorizar a Bíblia ou outra obra qualquer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Memorera bibeln eller någonting annat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Вивчення напам'ять Біблії або будь-яких інших текстів</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxMemorize the Bible or anything elsexx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>TotalReqall is a memorization tool which allows memorizing the Bible in many different translations, as well as memorizing any other content you want to.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El TotalReqall és una eina de memorització que permet memoritzar la Bíblia en moltes traduccions diferents, així com qualsevol altre contingut que vulgueu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El TotalReqall és una eina de memorització que permet memoritzar la Bíblia en moltes traduccions diferents, així com qualsevol altre contingut que vulgueu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">TotalReqall es una herramienta de memorización que le permite memorizar la Biblia en muchas traducciones distintas, así como memorizar cualquier otro tipo de contenido que desee.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">TotalReqall is een hulpmiddel voor memoriseren voor het memoriseren van Bijbelteksten in vele verschillende vertalingen, evenals het memoriseren van elke andere inhoud die u zou willen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O TotalReqall é uma ferramenta de memorização que lhe permite memorizar a Bíblia nas suas várias traduções, assim como memorizar qualquer outro conteúdo que desejar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">TotalReqall är ett memoreringsverktyg som gör det möjligt att memorera bibeln med många olika översättningar, samt memorera vilket annat innehåll som du vill.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">TotalReqall — інструмент для вивчення текстів напам'ять, за допомогою якого ви можете вивчати напам'ять уривки з Біблії у багатьох різних перекладах, а також вивчати напам'ять будь-які інші тексти.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxTotalReqall is a memorization tool which allows memorizing the Bible in many different translations, as well as memorizing any other content you want to.xx</p>
    <p>TotalReqall uses the Sword library to manage Biblical texts. This makes it simple to add new translations to TotalReqall by simply installing a new Sword module on your system.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El TotalReqall usa la biblioteca Sword per a gestionar els texts bíblics. Això facilita afegir traduccions noves al TotalReqall instal·lant un mòdul Sword nou al sistema.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El TotalReqall usa la biblioteca Sword per a gestionar els texts bíblics. Això facilita afegir traduccions noves al TotalReqall instal·lant un mòdul Sword nou al sistema.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">TotalReqall usa la biblioteca Sword para gestionar textos bíblicos. Facilita la adición de nuevas traducciones a TotalReqall con solo instalar un nuevo módulo de Sword en el sistema.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">TotalReqall gebruikt de Sword bibliotheek om Bijbelse teksten te beheren. Dit maakt het eenvoudig om nieuwe vertalingen aan TotalReqall toe te voegen door eenvoudig een nieuwe Sword module op uw systeem te installeren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O TotalReqall usa a biblioteca Sword para gerir os textos Bíblicos. Isto simplifica a adição de novas traduções ao TotalReqall, instalando para tal um novo módulo do Sword no seu sistema.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">TotalReqall använder biblioteket Sword för att hantera bibliska texter. Det gör det enkelt att lägga till nya översättningar i TotalReqall genom att helt enkelt installera en ny modul i Sword på systemet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Для керування текстами з Біблії у TotalReqall використано бібліотеку Sword. Це спрощує додавання нових перекладів до TotalReqall — достатньо просто встановити новий модуль Sword у вашій системі.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxTotalReqall uses the Sword library to manage Biblical texts. This makes it simple to add new translations to TotalReqall by simply installing a new Sword module on your system.xx</p>
    <p>For custom content, merely enter what you want to memorize, along with a unique title for identification. Then you can memorize it just like you would memorize a Bible verse.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Per al contingut personalitzat, només introduïu el que vulgueu memoritzar amb un títol únic com a identificació. Després ho podreu memoritzar de la mateixa manera que memoritzaríeu un versicle de la Bíblia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Per al contingut personalitzat, només introduïu el que vulgueu memoritzar amb un títol únic com a identificació. Després ho podreu memoritzar de la mateixa manera que memoritzaríeu un versicle de la Bíblia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Para contenido personalizado, introduzca simplemente lo que desee memorizar junto con un título único a modo de identificación. A continuación podrá memorizarlo como haría con un versículo de la Biblia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Voor eigen inhoud, voer gewoon wat u wilt memoriseren in, samen met een unieke titel voor identificatie. Daarna kunt u het memoriseren net als u een Bijbelvers zou doen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Para o conteúdo personalizado, simplesmente introduza o que deseja memorizar, em conjunto com um título único para a identificação. Agora pode memorizá-lo como faria com um verso da Bíblia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">För eget innehåll, skriv helt enkelt in vad du vill memorera, tillsammans med en unik titel för identifikation. Sedan kan du memorera det precis som du skulle memorera en bibelvers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Для роботи із іншими текстами достатньо просто ввести текст для вивчення напам'ять і вказати унікальну назву для ідентифікації цього тексту. Далі можна вивчати текст напам'ять у той самий спосіб, у який ви можете вивчати напам'ять вірші з Біблії.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFor custom content, merely enter what you want to memorize, along with a unique title for identification. Then you can memorize it just like you would memorize a Bible verse.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=totalreqall</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=totalreqall</url>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.totalreqall.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>The TotalReqall welcome page</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">La pàgina de benvinguda del TotalReqall</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">La pàgina de benvinguda del TotalReqall</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">La página de bienvenida de TotalReqall</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">De welkomstpagina van TotalReqall</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">A página de boas-vindas do TotalReqall</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Välkomstsidan för TotalReqall</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Початкова сторінка TotalReqall</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxThe TotalReqall welcome pagexx</caption>
      <image>
        https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/totalreqall/welcome.png
      </image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Choosing a verse</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Triar un versicle</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Triar un versicle</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Escoger un versículo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Een vers kiezen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Escolher um verso</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Välja en vers</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Вибір вірша</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxChoosing a versexx</caption>
      <image>
        https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/totalreqall/choose-verse.png
      </image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Entering custom content</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Introduir contingut personalitzat</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Introduir contingut personalitzat</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Introducción de contenido personalizado</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Eigen inhoud invoeren</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Introduzir conteúdo personalizado</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Skriva in eget innehåll</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Введення нетипових даних</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxEntering custom contentxx</caption>
      <image>
        https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/totalreqall/custom-content.png
      </image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Selecting a saved item to memorize</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Seleccionar un element desat a memoritzar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Seleccionar un element guardat a memoritzar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Selección de un elemento guardado para memorizarlo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Een opgeslagen item om te memoriseren selecteren</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Seleccionar um item gravado para memorizar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Välja ett sparat objekt att memorera</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Вибір збереженого запису для вивчення напам'ять</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxSelecting a saved item to memorizexx</caption>
      <image>
        https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/totalreqall/saved-content.png
      </image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Memorizing a verse</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Memoritzar un versicle</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Memoritzar un versicle</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Memorizar un versículo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Een vers memoriseren</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Memorizar um verso</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Memorera en vers</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Вивчення вірша напам'ять</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxMemorizing a versexx</caption>
      <image>
        https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/totalreqall/memorizing.png
      </image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>totalreqall</binary>
  </provides>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <value key="KDE::matrix">#totalreqall:kde.org</value>
  <value key="KDE::irc">#kde-totalreqall</value>
</component>
